Guide to the Committee on Christian Literature For Women and Children in Mission Fields, Inc. Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum, 1918-1986; Series VII
  - Executive Files: Marion Van Horne
    - Workshops
      - Workshops: Ireland 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Workshops: Jerusalem 1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Workshops: Nairobi, Kenya 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Workshops: Nairobi, Kenya 1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Workshops: Korea 1959 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Workshops: Lebanon 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Workshops: Mexico 1959 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Workshops: Mexico 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Workshops: Nepal 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Workshops: New Guinea 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Workshops: Malaysia 1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Workshops: South Africa 1968 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Workshops: South Africa 1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Workshops: South Pacific 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Workshops: Tanzania 1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Workshops: Thailand 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Workshops: Thailand 1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Workshops: Turkey 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Workshops: Zambia 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Workshops: Proposed, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - A Survey Report on the Training of Writers, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Lists of Books Published, 1969-1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Developmental Literature for Women, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Histories and Publications
    - Publicity Brochures (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Program Booklet – The Talking Leaf (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Program Booklet, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "A Woman's Place" (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "A Book in Hand" (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "ask any woman" (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Word at Work
      - Record of Mailings (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Themes (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Analysis (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - The Word at Work, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - The Word at Work, selected issues, 1959-1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - The Word at Work, selected issues, 1970-1982 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Photographs
    - Workshops: India, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Workshops: Korea, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Workshops: Warwick, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Workshops: Brazil, 1974, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Workshops: Egypt, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Workshops: South Africa, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Year of the Child poster photo (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 18, Folder 28)